对不起  你是谁
I'm sorry. Who the hell are you?
亚瑟·凯奇  英国记录者
Arthur Ketch. British Men of Letters.
(忆往昔)
刚刚那是枪榴弹发射器吗
Was that a grenade launcher?
是的
Quite.
我们愿意合作
We're eager to collaborate.
你们并没有看到我们最好的一面
You haven't exactly seen us at our best.
她企图杀我们
She tried to kill us.
你只想帮助这对儿美国猎人
And all you wanna do is help these American Hunters
清理这个国家的怪物
to clear this country of monsters?
我们可以提供专业知识  武器
We can offer expertise, weaponry.
玩具最好玩了
The toys are the fun part.
你要用那个把路西法从总统身体里赶出去
So you're gonna pop Lucifer out of the President with that?
我们知道你怀孕了
We know you're pregnant.
那不是个孩子  那是路西法的后代
This is not a baby. This is the spawn of Lucifer.
我不能  我是它的母亲
I can't do it. I'm its mother.
我来给你描绘一下
Let me paint you a picture
一个再没有人会因为超自然生灵而死的世界
of a world where no one has to die because of the supernatural.
继续说
I'm listening.
(如今)
好了
So...
给我讲个故事
Tell me a story.
(下午5点20分)
曼迪  是阿曼达的昵称吗
Mandy. That short for Amanda?
当然了
Duh.
嗯  我要个奶酪汉堡吧
Yeah, I'll -- I'll go with the cheeseburger.
嗯
Oh, yeah.
这里的无线网络密码是什么
Hey, what's the, uh, Wi-Fi password here?
-多加奶酪  -不不  普通就行
- Extra cheese. - No, no. Just, uh, as it is, is fine.
密码  是"多加奶酪"
That's the password. "extra cheese."
听上去不赖
You know what? That sounds good.
我也改成要奶酪汉堡吧
I'm gonna change mine to a cheeseburger as well.
多加奶酪  我要多吃点碳水化合物
Extra cheese. I wanna carbo-load.
-奶酪不是碳水化合物  -奶酪不是碳水化合物
- Cheese isn't a carb. - Cheese isn't a carbohydrate.
好吧
Well....
牛排鸡蛋  一分熟
Steak and eggs. Bloody.
你呢  帅哥
And how 'bout you, handsome?
什么
What?
日出特餐  谢谢
Sunrise Special, please.
好的
Nice.
哥们  她看上你了
Dude, she is into you.
迪恩
‭Dean...
不  这是好事
No, this is good.
我们一直想找到合适的教学时机
We've been looking for teachable moments.
这...
This...
一切还好吧  妈妈
Everything all right, Mom?
就是个猎人  需要帮助
Yeah, just a hunter, needs some help.
又一个
Another one?
这一行多交朋友是没错的
Can't have too many friends in this line of work.
-好吧  -这里的网络好糟
- Okay - ‭The Internet here sucks.
我把地堡的文件都下载到了新档案馆里
I downloaded all the bunker's files to a new archive,
-但这里没信号  我...  -没人在乎
- but we're not getting any signal, so I'm j... - Nobody cares.
小卡  关于服务员  你要知道
Cass, here's the thing you need to know about waitresses, okay?
她们成天被人泡  你得拿出最佳水平来
They get hit on all day long, so you gotta bring you A-game.
但好处是  她们总是一身食物味儿
But upside? They always smell like food.
总是一身食物味儿
They always smell like food.
-好了  -一身食物味儿为什么是好处
- Okay -- Okay - ‭Why is upside they smell like food?
是吧  多棒
Right? It's great.
你为什么喜欢她们有食物味儿
Why would you want them to smell like food?
放下平板  抬起头  闭上嘴
Screens down, eyes up, shut up.
-抱歉  妈妈  -抱歉
- Sorry, Mom. - Sorry.
好了  情况是这样的
Okay, here's what we know.
目标出行很规律
Our target keeps a tight schedule.
他每晚8点走
He leaves every day at 8:00 p.m.
8点45分准时回来
He gets back exactly at 8:45.
-他去干什么  -夜间钓鱼
- What's he doin'? - Night fishing.
等等  你叫我们来
Wait a minute, you called us to --
杀一个喜欢钓鱼的恶魔
to kill a demon that likes to fish?
是的  这一切对我来说很陌生
Yes, I did. Look, guys, this is all new to me.
法国狼人问题
All right, you got a rugaru problem?
找我没错  但恶魔
Hey, I'm your guy. But demons?
天啊  是这样  我经过这里
Hell. Look, I was just passing through
听说发生了残杀牲畜的事
and I heard about some cattle mutilations.
典型的恶魔手法
Classic demon sign.
我开始深挖
I started to dig.
这里还有很多处女失踪
A lot of virgins go missing around here, too.
典型的色鬼恶魔手法
Classic horny demon sign.
所以沃利找了我们求助
Which is why Wally called us, asking for help.
计划都清楚了吧
So are we all clear on the plan?
来了
Incoming.
曼迪  问你个问题
Mandy? Question for you.
我这位害羞但帅得惨绝人寰的朋友
My shy but devastatingly handsome friend here
想问你
was, uh, just wondering,
你什么时候下班
when do you get off?
随时
Whenever I can.
姑娘真棒  就这么丢下一句
Point 1 for her. Just dropped that on the table.
还当着我们所有人
Right in front of all of us, too.
好了  网络有信号了  我们干正事吧
All right, Internet's up. We're in business.
我好紧张
I'm so nervous,
我都不知道我吃不吃得下去
I don't even know if I can eat.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be fine.
萨姆和迪恩呢
Where's Sam and Dean?
不  不
No! No!
沃利  那是...不
Wally? Is that a -- No!
我要出名了
I'm gonna be famous. ‭
杀死萨姆·温彻斯特的恶魔
The demon that killed Sam Winchester.
我会成为传奇
They're gonna tell stories about me.
不会的
No, they won't.
[邪恶力量 第12季第12集]
(受伤天使)
我们每个人的肉身都会死去
Each of us has a time when the physical body dies
我们最终都要面临上帝的审判
and we all face God's judgment in the end.
这世上没有一个人
There's not one of us alive walking on this earthly plane
可以不用为行为付出代价
that will not pay the consequence for their actions.
上帝将把我们持于掌中
The Lord will hold us in the palm of his hand
掂量我们的灵魂
and he'll weigh our souls.
兄弟姐妹们  你们够格吗
Brothers and sisters, are you worthy?
(早些时候)
妈妈
Mom.
萨姆
Sam.
迪恩
Dean.
这是沃利
Wally.
他们是我儿子
These are my sons.
很高兴认识你  她说了你不少好话
Glad to meet you. She said a lot of good things.
你们也是
Yeah. Right back at you, man.
你们妈妈很为你们骄傲
Your, uh, your mom's real proud of you boys.
小卡
Cass.
谢谢你来  我知道你很忙
Thanks for coming. I know you're busy.
也没有
Well, not really.
怎么样  路西法的孩子还没下落
So, what? No luck with Lucifer's kid?
没有  凯莉·克莱恩  她...
No, Kelly Kline -- it's like she's...
消失了
just disappeared.
路西法的孩子  是个笑话吧
Lucifer's kid. That's a joke, right? The...
不是笑话
It's not a joke.
好吧  各位  我们上路吧
All right, ramblers, let's get rambling.
路西法有孩子
Lucifer has a kid?
-这里的无线网络密码是什么  -多加奶酪
- What's the, uh, Wi-Fi password here? - Extra cheese.
计划都清楚了吧
Everyone is clear on the plan?
10点45分  恶魔回家
At 10:45, demon comes home.
萨姆和我会等着他
Sam and I will be waiting for him.
我用恶魔陷阱子弹打他
I'll pop him with a Devil's Trap bullet.
我用恶魔刀了结他
I'll finish him off with a demon blade.
我跟你守在后门
And I will wait at the back with you
以防他走那边
in case he comes in that way.
-好啊  我做什么  -盯梢  别死了
- Cool, cool. What do I do? - Keep a lookout. Don't die.
一切都会没事的
Everything is gonna be fine.
玛丽
Mary?
你去哪了
Where were you?
厕所
Bathroom.
我有时会紧张
I get nervous sometimes.
尿尿
Urination.
我理解
I understand.
沃利
‭Wally?
小心  玛丽  他早回来了
Heads up, Mary. He's coming back early.
可以解释下为什么闯进我家吗
You mind explainin' why you broke into my house?
不会仅仅是为了毁掉我的晚间垂钓
I know it wasn't just to ruin the evening catch.
猎人
Hunters.
这不好使
Well, that didn't work.
天使
Angel.
你好啊  亲爱的
Hiya, sweetheart.
快跑
Run!
各位  我们有麻烦了
Guys, we got a problem.
-我们知道  -不  来了好多恶魔
- Yeah, we know. - No, you don't. Demons incoming.
去找妈妈和小卡  我们能行的  快去
All right, get to Mom and Cass. We got this. Go.
准备好了吗
You ready?
凡事总有第一次
First time for everything.
我好久没见过天使了
Been a long time since I've seen an angel.
嗯
Yeah.
还不够久
But not long enough.
那是...不
Is that a -- No! No! No!
你想去哪
Where do you think you're going, huh?
来嘛
Come on.
小卡  天呐
Cass. Oh, my...
-他在哪  -我不知道
- Where is he? - I don't know.
-他在哪  -走吧
- Where is he? - Come on.
你可以自愈吗
Can you heal yourself?
我试了  不对劲
I tried. Something's wrong.
多严重
How bad is it?
萨姆
Sam.
你在哪
Hey, where are you?
沿路找到的农场  似乎废弃了
Farm down the road. It looks abandoned.
第一个路口左转  开到一个谷仓那里
Take your first left and drive until you see a barn.
好的  我们就来  你没事吧
Yeah, okay. We're on the way. Are you okay?
有事
No.
(晚上9点5分)
刚刚怎么回事
What the hell just happened?
沃利呢
Where's Wally?
沃利...
Wally, uh...
天呐
Oh, God.
小卡
Cass?
妈妈  那些其他恶魔哪来的
Mom, where did those other demons come from?
我不知道
I don't know. I...
-目标  你看到...  -没有
- The target. Did you see - No.
我们对他使的招都不好用
He brushed off everything we threw at him.
-你看到他的眼睛了吗  -什么
- Did you see his eyes? - What?
是黄色的
They were yellow.
他有黄眼
He had yellow eyes.
妈妈
Mom...
你给我们惹上了什么事
what the hell did you get us into?
(妈妈玛丽)
(11小时前  上午10点7分)
就是他吗
That's him?
那就是你需要人帮忙的坏恶魔
That's the big bad demon you need help with?
就是个老头子
Just some old guy.
严格讲  我已经60多了
Technically, I'm in my 60s.
好吧
Okay, then.
我知道什么
Hell, what do I know?
我从未追杀过恶魔
I've never gone after a demon before.
我都不知道你为什么叫我来
I don't even know why you called me.
因为如果萨姆和迪恩以为他们是在帮你而不是我
Because if Sam and Dean think they're helping you and not me,
他们就不会问不该问的了
they won't ask the wrong questions.
这样更安全
It's safer that way.
好吧
Right.
那是你的新英国朋友给的
You get those from your new limey friends?
那什么高大上的记录者
Them fancy Men of Letters?
是的
I did.
你信任他们
You trust 'em?
就是...我听过他们的推销
I-I just mean, I-I heard the sales pitch --
钱  装备
money, gear.
听上去是不错
It all sounds swell,
但有人跑来给你这  给你那
but someone walks up to you and offers you something
感觉好得不真实
that sounds a little too good to be true?
究竟有什么附加条件呢
I wonder, what's the catch?
我跟他们合作后
Since I've been working with them,
已经除掉了十几个吸血鬼巢
we've taken out more than a dozen vamp nests,
四个狼人族群
four werewolf packs,
还有一个在阿林顿横行的食尸鬼
and a ghoul who was eating his way through Arlington.
我们救了很多人
We saved a lot of people.
好吧  那你的确信任他们
Right, so you do trust them.
走吧
Let's go.
嗯
Yeah. ‭
曼迪  你什么时候下班
Hey, Mandy, when do you get off?
随时
Whenever I can.
你们见过那帮高大上的记录者吗
You meet them fancy Men of Letters?
英国记录者吗
British Men of Letters?
是啊  他们有装备
Yeah, they got gear,
但他们企图杀我弟弟
but, uh, you know, they tried to kill my brother.
好了  网络有信号了  我们干正事吧
All right, Internet's up. We're in business.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be fine.
(晚上8点23分)
似乎没有符文保护
Doesn't appear to be warded.
好了  我们开工吧
Okay. Let's get to work.
萨姆
Sam?
迪恩呢
Where's Dean?
他去藏车了
Uh, he's out stashing the car.
-好  -等等  妈妈
- Okay. - ‭Wait, Mom?
我只想确保
I just wanted to make sure that, um...
你没事
you're okay.
我知道
I mean, I know...
你并不想要这样的生活
you never really wanted this.
生活什么时候是如你所愿了
Since when is life about getting what you want?
玛丽
Mary?
你去哪了
Where were you?
厕所
Bathroom.
我有时会紧张
I get nervous sometimes.
这不好使
Well, that didn't work.
(晚上9点3分)
(霍比特人  你做了什么  那恶魔有黄眼)
(不怪我们  情报不准  你不能留在那里  他会找到你的)
玛丽
Mary.
Mary. ‭
你还好吗
How you feeling?
刚刚怎么回事
What the hell just happened?
沃利呢
Where's Wally?
沃利...
Wally, uh...
天呐
Oh, God.
小卡
‭Cass?
妈妈  那些其他恶魔哪来的
Mom, where did those other demons come from?
我不知道
I don't know.
你看上去糟透了
You look like hammered crap.
是啊  差不多
Yeah, that sounds about right.
我看看
Let's see.
好了  好吧
All right, okay. ‭
嗯嗯  告诉你
Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, hey, you know what?
-我经历过更糟的  -是吗  什么时候
- I've had worse. - ‭Oh, yeah? When?
迪恩  不对劲  我...
Dean, something's wrong. I...
我无法自愈
I can't heal myself.
我觉得...
I think the...
那恶魔的矛上有毒
I think the demon's s-spear was poisoned.
我不...
I don't...
我觉得我要死了
I-I think I'm dying.
不  你就是需要时间  好吗
No. No, you just need some time, okay?
你会像以前那样好起来的
You'll heal up the old-fashioned way.
妈妈
Mom... ‭
-你给我们惹上了什么事  -萨姆
- what the hell did you get us into? - ‭Sam.
萨姆
Sammy!
你们这些白痴
You idiots!
你们都要死了
You're all going to die.
你们这些白痴  你们都要死了
You idiots! You're all going to die.
今天真是越来越妙了
Well, this day just keeps gettin' better.
克劳力
Crowley?
就是你吗
You're him?
地狱之王
The King of Hell?
你是温家的妈妈吧
You must be Mother Winchester.
幸会  听过你好多事迹
Pleasure. I've heard so much.
你敢碰我  我就杀了你
Touch me and I'll kill you.
毛毛怎么了
What's up with Feathers?
你来干什么
What are you even doing here?
-你怎么找到我们的  -等等
- How'd you find us? - Wait a second.
那些恶魔  是你的
The demons. They were yours.
-显然的  -他们杀了我的朋友
- Obviously. - ‭They killed my friend.
你的朋友犯了蠢  你们都...
Your friend was stupid. You're all...
知道你们做了什么吗
Do you know what you've done?
知道雷米尔这个名字吗
Does the name Ramiel mean anything to you?
-不  -知道
- No. - ‭Yes.
什么
What?
雷米尔  地狱王子
Ramiel, Prince of Hell.
雷米尔  地狱王子  很上口  挺押韵
Ramiel, Prince of Hell. It's catchy. It rhymes.
他会杀了你们每一个人
And he's going to kill each and every one of you.
不  王子都死了
No. The Princes are all dead.
那是我们放出去的话  让人们放弃寻找
That's what we told people to stop them looking.
但实际上  不是这样的
But in reality, not so much.
地狱王子是什么
W-what the hell is a Prince of...Hell?
是最古老的恶魔
The oldest of the old demons.
莉莉丝之后的第一代
The first generation after Lilith.
路西法亲自转化了他们
Lucifer turned them him himself,
亚特兰蒂斯是之后才沉入海底的
before the oceans drank Atlantis.
他们是受训将军
They were trained to be generals,
带领恶魔大军与天堂作战
to lead demonic armies in the war against Heaven.
就像亚撒色
Like Azazel.
他们眼睛都一样
They even have his eyes.
(六年前)
你是谁
Who are you?
你想干什么
And what do you want?
我是克劳力
The name's Crowley.
(克劳力先生)
十字路口之王
King of the Crossroads?
我是地狱派来的
I've been sent by Hell.
怎么  地狱不教敲门吗
And what? Don't they teach you how to knock in hell?
我道歉
For that, I apologize.
但我带来了礼物
But I do come bearing gifts.
第一个来自全体恶魔
The first is from all demonkind.
我们听说你收集武器
We heard that you collect weapons --
越古老越好
the more ancient and arcane, the better.
容我呈上
So may I present
大天使米迦勒的长矛
the Lance of Michael, the Archangel.
了不起
Impressive.
这个美人  杀小鬼干净利落
This beauty, she kills the bad ones fast
杀好士兵缓慢痛苦
and the good ones slow and painful.
真讽刺  这可是天使打造的
Ironic, seeing as it was made by an angel.
米迦勒只想杀一个天使
There's only one angel Michael wanted to kill,
他想要那个混蛋好好受折磨
and he wanted that son of a bitch to suffer.
魔法
The magic.
都在符文上
It's all in the runework.
还有工艺
The craftsmanship.
第二件礼物  来自我
The second gift is from myself.
是我的心意
Personally.
我觉得你可能会喜欢
Something I thought you might like.
你从哪弄到的
Where did you get this?
有些人随便乱放的东西真是不可思议
It's amazing what some people just leave laying about.
就算是你的加冕礼物了
Consider it your coronation present.
什么
Pardon?
这就要说到最后一件礼物了
Brings me to your final gift --
地狱王座
the Throne of Hell.
你要我去当王
You want me to be king?
莉莉丝和亚撒色都死了
Well, with Lilith and Azazel dead,
路西法又关回了笼子  我们需要个统治者
and Lucifer back in his box, we need a ruler.
而你是顺位继承人  雷米尔
You are next in line, Ramiel.
地狱王子
Prince of Hell.
就是个称号
It's just a name.
没有什么意义
Doesn't mean anything.
但是  只要你愿意  王位就是你的
Still, the crown is yours if you want it.
我不愿意
I don't.
你坐吧
You take it.
我...
I...
什么
Pardon?
你似乎挺有野心
You seem ambitious enough,
也挺有计谋
conniving enough,
够狡猾
slimy enough.
去坐吧
So take it!
追求荣誉吧  孩子
Go for the glory, kid.
梦想是一回事
I mean, one dares to dream,
但其他人怎么办
but what about the others?
你不是唯一的王子
You're not the only prince.
亚撒色是个狂徒
Azazel was a fanatic,
真正相信路西法的大计划
a true believer in Lucifer's master plan.
但我们其他人  老实说
But the rest of us? Well, the truth is,
我们早就不在乎了
we stopped caring a long time ago.
阿斯摩太有他的爱好  大衮有她的玩物
Asmodeus has his hobbies. Dagon has her toys.
我们对自己很满足
We're happy where we are.
如果你想要王冠  归你了
So if you want the crown, it's yours.
否则
Otherwise...
当然...
Oh, hell, ye--
我要了
I'll take it.
我勉为其难地接受了
I mean, I graciously accept.
太好了  还有一件事
Swell, but there is one thing.
天上不掉馅饼
Nothing comes without a price.
这会很简单的
Well, this should be easy enough.
别再来找我们
Leave us alone.
确保也不会有其他人来找我们
And make sure everyone else does the same.
如果有人  有什么  打扰了地狱王子
If anyone -- anything -- bothers a Prince of Hell,
那就怪你了  克劳力
that's gonna be on your head, Crowley.
你不会想知道惹我们生气
And you don't wanna know what happens
会有怎样的下场
when you piss us off.
我恭敬地接受你的条件
I humbly accept your terms.
我的恶魔是为了保护雷米尔免遭骚扰的
My demons were there to keep people away from Ramiel.
相信我  那是个马蜂窝
Believe me, that's a hornet's nest
你们不能去捅
you do not want to be kicking.
太迟了
Too late.
小卡是怎么了
What happened to Cass?
你说呢
You tell me.
他被一个银尖的矛刺了
He got stabbed with some kind of silver-tipped spear.
不是矛
It's not a spear.
是长矛
It's a lance.
米迦勒的长矛
The Lance of Michael.
米迦勒
Michael.
那个大天使吗
As in Michael Michael?
很厉害的东西
Nasty bit of business.
碰到谁都会死
Kills everything it touches.
恶魔会化成烟
If you're a demon, you go up in a puff of smoke.
天使
If you're an angel,
会慢慢死去
you just...rot away.
抱歉  卡西迪奥
Sorry, Castiel.
不  不行
No. No.
肯定有解药
There's a cure.
总是有解药的  我们会找到的
There's always a cure, and we will find it.
-怎么找  -抓住雷米尔
- How? - ‭We trap Ramiel.
揍扁他  直到他交出解药
And we beat his ass until he gives it up.
不会有用的
It's not gonna work.
我们战胜过黑暗和魔鬼
We took down the Darkness and the Devil.
你们花了数年才打败路西法
It took you years to defeat Lucifer,
而且是上帝帮忙才阻止了黑暗
and the power of God to stop the Darkness.
如果你们还有时间  或许能制服雷米尔
Maybe if you had more time, you could manage Ramiel.
但现在  在这间谷仓里
But right now, in this barn...
我本来都有点喜欢唱诗班小子了
I was growing fond of the choir boy, too.
闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up. Shut up.
我们没时间跟你废话
We don't have time, okay, for your -- for you.
你要么帮忙  要么滚蛋
So either help us or get the hell out of here!
猜到了
Yeah, figures.
(晚上9点7分)
我要怎么做  你才不会进那个谷仓
What can I do to keep you out of that barn?
我闻到那天使了
I smell the angel.
他不行了
He's rotting.
那些人
These people --
是你的朋友吗
they your friends?
我没有朋友
I don't have friends.
我跟我用得上的人做交易
I make deals with those I can use.
每个王国都需要盟友  包括地狱
Every kingdom needs allies, even Hell.
盟友  你就这么称呼那三个加起来
Allies. Is that what you call three humans
只有一个好肝脏的人类和一个坏掉的天使吗
with one good liver between them and a busted up angel?
我承认  他们看上去没什么特别
I admit, they don't sound like much.
但每次世界末日
But every Armageddon,
每次"一切将终结于此"的状况
every bloody "This is the end of all things,"
都是温家人阻止的
a Winchester stopped it.
不管怎样  他们是我们不能失去的财富
Like it or not, they're an asset we can't afford to lose.
我们说好的  克劳力
We had an agreement, Crowley.
不许来打扰我们
No one bothers us.
记得吗
You remember?
我们做过一次协议
We made one deal.
再做一个吧
Let's make another.
怎么样
What do you say?
(终极对决)
我们没时间跟你废话
We don't have time, okay, for your -- for you.
你要么帮忙  要么滚蛋
So either help us or get the hell out of here!
猜到了
Yeah, figures.
(晚上9点12分)
小卡  多严重
Cass, how bad is it?
克劳力是对的  你们还是走吧
Crowley's right. You should go.
-小卡  得了  -不  听我说
- Cass, come on. - No, you listen to me.
你...听着  谢谢
You -- Look, thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
认识你们
Knowing you, it...
是我这辈子最棒的事
it's been the best part of my life.
我们一同
And the things that...
经历的那些事
the things we've shared together,
已经改变了我
they have changed me.
你们是我的家人
You're my family.
我爱你们
I love you.
我爱你们所有人
I love all of you.
求你们
Just please...
别让我临终末了
please, don't make my last moments be spent
还要看着你们死
watching you die.
跑吧
Just run.
自保吧
Save yourselves.
我会尽量拖住雷米尔
And I will hold Ramiel off as long as I can.
小卡  不
Cass, no.
跑吧
Yes.
你们得继续战斗
You need to keep fighting.
我们是在战斗
We are fighting.
我们在为你而战  小卡
We're fighting for you, Cass.
就像你说的  你是家人
And like you said, you're family.
我们不会丢下家人
And we don't leave family behind.
妈妈
Mom.
怎么办
What's the play?
我们使出所有招数
We hit him with everything we got.
雷米尔
Ramiel.
好极了
Toasty.
你伤了我们一个朋友
You stabbed one of our friends.
你朋友擅闯了
Your friend was trespassing.
告诉我们怎么治好他
Tell us how to cure him.
没有解药
There is no cure.
知道我们是谁吗
You have any idea who we are?
我不在乎
I don't care.
我不在乎你们是谁  你们为什么来
I don't care who you are. I don't care why you're here.
我不在乎天堂或地狱什么的
I don't care about Heaven or Hell or anything.
我甚至不在乎路西法要有娃了
I don't even care that Lucifer's got a bun in the oven.
这你也知道
You know about that?
我妹妹大衮  她对此颇为关切
My sister Dagon, she's taken an interest.
-但我  -我猜猜
- But me? - Let me guess.
你不在乎
You don't care.
我只想不被打扰
All I wanted was to be left alone.
然后你们来了
But then you come.
你们偷我的东西
You...steal from me.
这...我不能忍受
And that? Ooh. That I cannot abide.
把我的东西还我
Give me back what's mine,
否则我就从你们的尸体上拿走
or I take it off your lifeless bodies.
你们有...
You've got...
30秒
30 seconds.
显然  我们不知道你在说什么
Obviously, we got no idea what you're talking about.
20秒
20 seconds.
那随你们
Have it your way.
小卡
Cass.
伙计  有我们呢  小卡
Hey, buddy. Hey, we're here, Cass.
我们在这儿呢  伙计
We're right here, buddy.
魔法
The magic.
都在符文上
It's all in the runework.
还有工艺
The craftsmanship.
撑住  好吗  我们怎么办
Hang in there, all right? What do we do?
魔法在工艺上
The magic's in the craftsmanship.
小卡
Cass?
不客气
You're welcome.
你没事了
So...you're good?
我想是的
I guess so.
他刚刚...
What did he...
他说什么偷他的东西
What did he mean about somebody stealing from him?
谁知道那疯子说什么呢
Who knows what that crazy man was talkin' about.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
(最后一件事)
真是
Well, that's...
好个故事
quite a story.
你干得不错
You did well.
你叫我去杀一个地狱王子
You sent me after a damn Prince of Hell.
我们并不知道他是什么
Well, we didn't know what he was.
我们只知道他有那件东西
We just knew he had the item.
这不叫借口
That's not good enough.
我失去了一个朋友  还差点失去一个孩子
I lost a friend. I almost lost one of my boys.
-我们道歉  -闭嘴
- And we apologize - ‭Shut up.
再发生这样的事
Anything like that happens again -- anything --
我就灭了你
and I will burn you down.
你们所有人
All of you.
这是威胁吗
Is that a threat?
是承诺
It's a promise.
我们犯了个错误
We made a mistake.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我可以看看吗
Can I...see it?
你好  美人
Hello, beautiful.
我父亲以前跟我讲过它的故事
My father used to tell me stories about this thing.
所有生灵里只有五个
You know there's only five things in all Creation
它杀不掉
it can't kill?
是啊
Oh, yes.
我很了解这把柯尔特枪
I know all about the Colt.
搜那间屋子
Search that house.
再搜一遍
Search it again.
找到那把枪
Find me that gun.
*有把枪称霸西部*
*Oh, there was a gun that won the West*
*有个男人世间无双*
*There was a man among the best*
*那枪那人都出手如神*
*The fastest gun or man alive*
*柯尔特枪出击犹如闪电*
*A lightning bolt when he shot that Colt*
*四十五*
*Forty five*
天呐
Man.
你觉得这很好笑吧
‭I suppose you think that's funny.
我见过那表情
I know that look.
萨姆和迪恩打败了你
Sam and Dean have got you down.
我还是无法相信
Well, I still can't believe
你在给那对莽汉帮忙
that you're working for the Dukes of Haphazard.
你真觉得他们在乎你吗
Do you really think they care about you?
想想看  克劳力
I mean, think about it, Crowley.
他们杀你的同类
They kill your kind.
那是他们的血脉
It's in their blood.
你知道
And you know...
you know...
他们迟早会找上你来
it's only a matter of time before they come... for you.
闭嘴  狗狗
Shut your mouth, dog.
那不是我的名字
That's not my name.